DAVID BALDUS PAPERS (APAP329) 1965-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Pennsylvania Research, 1992-2011; 11; 40.5
  - Charging and Sentencing Study, 1996-2004; 11.1; 10.4
    - Data Reports - PTWEIGH3, 1998 July 10 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Data Summeries - Ethnicity issues, hispanic crosstabs, 1998 July 10 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Data Reports - AG MIT IB, PTWEIGH2, 1998 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Data Reports - AGG MIT IB, PTWEIGH3, 1998 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Data Reports - Cleaning AG MIT IB, 1998 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Data Summeries - Hung cases, 1998 July 11 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Data Reports - AG NO MIT, 1998 July 13 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Data Reports - Death J, 1998 July 13 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR, 1998 July 13 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - coding Aggravating Series 7 and Mitgating Series 9, 1998 July 15 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Data Reports - 2RS, PTWIGH3 without hearing, 1998 July 15 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Data Reports - Death-J, 1998 July 16 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR, 1998 July 16; 1998 August 17 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Data Reports - AGG FND, 1998 July 22 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Corrections listing of death row inmates and race, 1998 July 22 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Venire Study Update, 1998 July 24 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Data Reports - Alt measure PTDTHJR with hung jury, 1998 July 29; 1998 August 24 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Data Reports - Alternate Scales with hung jury, AGNOMIT5, 1998 July 29 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Data Reports - Alternate scales with hung jury, PTDTH-JR, 1998 July 29 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Data Reports - Death-J Alternate measures with hung cases, 1998 July 29 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Data Reports - PTWEIGH3, set scales, 1998 July 29-30 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Draft pf Retrial Motion based on charging and sentencing study, ca. 1998 July (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Data Reports - AGGFND with race, 1998 August 9 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Data Reports - Correlations, mitgation findings with race, 1998 August 9 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Philadelphia retrials code, 1998 August 10 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Data Reports - AGGFND with race, 1998 August 11 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Data Reports - Mitigating facotrs with rate, 1998 August 11 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Data Reports - RRSA without hearing, without safe, 1998 August 14-17 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Data Reports - Alternate measures without hung jury, AG NO MIT5, 1998 August 17 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Data Reports - Alternate measures without hung jury, PTWEIGH3, 1998 August 17 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Data Reports - Death-J, 1998 August 17 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Data Reports - Death-J, 1998 August 17 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR, 1998 August 17 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Notes - Counts for each model, 1998 August 17 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Data Reports - Death J, Alt measures without val and hung jury, 1998 August 18 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR without val and hung jury, 1998 August 18 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Data Reports - Ag No Mit 5, with hearing, without victim work, 1998 August 20 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Data Reports - Ag No Mit 5 without hearing, without victim work, 1998 August 20 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Data Reports - Death-J without hearing, 1998 August 20 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR model without hearing, 1998 August 20 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Data Reports - PTWEIGH 3 without hearing, 1998 August 20; 1998 September 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Data Reports - Ag No Mit 5 without hearing, 1998 August 20-24; 1998 September 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Data Reports - Vic work, 1998 August 20-25 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Data Reports - Ag No Mit 5 Agg BD, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Data Reports - Ag No Mit 5 Agg NBV, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Data Reports - Death - J Agg BD, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Data Reports - Death J Agg NBV, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR BD Agg, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR NBV Agg, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Data Reports - PTWEIGH3 Agg's BD, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Data Reports - PTWEIGH 3 Agg NBV, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Data Reports - Race of defendant, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Data Reports - Race of Victim, 1998 August 21 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Data Reports - Death J, Alt scale with hung jury, 1998 August 24 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Data Reports - Death-J models with hearing, 1998 August 24 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR models with hearing, 1998 August 24 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Data Reports - PTWEIGH 3 with hearing, 1998 August 24 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Data Reports - unadjusted by race, 1998 August 24 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - request from Mordecai Gorelick, 1998 August 25-26 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Data Reports - Hung cases, 1998 August 26 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Data Reports - Hung cases analysis, 1998 August 26 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Data Reports, notes - Final 2 RSA Models, 1998 August 26 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Data Reports - Race and hypothetical [?] item, 1998 August 26 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Data Reports - Regression Bases Scales without hung jury, 1998 August 26 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Data Reports - Ag No Mit 5 PHATS, 1998 August 31 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Data Reports - Plea Bargin models, 1998 August 31 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Data Reports - GW I RSK Screen, 1998 August 31 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Data Reports - No Mit D-J, 1998 August 31-September 10 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Data Reports - Regression Scales with hearing, 1998 September 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Data Reports - AgNoMit5 with hearing, with victim work, 1998 September 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Data Reports - Hung cases, 1998 September 1-17 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Data Reports - 3 way outcomes, death, 1998 September 1; 1999 September 14 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Data Reports - Mid range focus analysis, 1998 September 4 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Data Reports - Weighting Hypothesis, 1998 September 4 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Data Reports - Unadjusted with Volunteers, 1998 September 04 (Oversize 4, Item 1)
    - Data Reports - NoMit D-J, 1998 September 5 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Data Reports - GLT without RSK, 1998 September 10 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Data Reports- Agg Mit Race Broad, 1998 September 11 (Oversize 2, Item 1)
    - Data Reports - Race Correlations with Mitigation, 1998 September 11 (Oversize 5, Item 1)
    - Data Reports - Race Correlations with Mitigation, 1998 September 11 (Oversize 6, Item 1)
    - Data Reports - Regression with BD NBD, 1998 September 11 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Foot note insert - Low SES, 1998 September 14 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Data Reports - Mitigation and race adjusted for security scale 1998 September 14 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Data Reports - Mitigation and race adjusted for case security [?], 1998 September 14 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Mitigation Study codes, protocol, data collection instrument, 1998 September 15; 1999 November 20 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Data Reports - white defendant models, 1998 September 16 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Data Reports - Runs without no aggravating factor found and no hung jury, 1998 September 4; 1998 September 17 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Barbara Broffitt, alternate plea cases, 1998 September 20 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - Selective prosecution claim, 1998 September 22 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Data Reports, 1998 September 22 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Data Reports - Bench P trials, 1998 September 22-28 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Diagnostics, notes, 1998 September 24 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Brief - Commonweath v. Saharris Rollins, 1998 September 25 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Corresspondence, notes - inserts and edits for Cornell Law Review, 1998 September 27 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Data Reports, 1998 September 29 (Oversize 4, Item 2)
    - Data Reports - Juror Part 2 Screen, 1998 September (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Data Reports - Core Models with 5 hispanic recoded to black, 1998 October 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Data Reports - models with non-black equal white only with 5 recodes, 1998 October 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Data Reports - 9 RS Models, black and white only defendant, 1998 October 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Data Reports - Models with hispanic defendant v. other defandants, 1998 October 3 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Data Reports - Models with white defandants defected, 1998 October 3 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Data Reports - Hispanic and white disparties, 1998 October 3 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Tables - David Baldus edits, 1999 October 3 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Data Reports - Scale, white vs. black crosstabs, 1998 October 5 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Data Reports - Unroute[?] statistics, 1998 October 5 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - article authors, 1998 October 6-8 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Data Reports - Impact of race victim on NoMit and number of death sentence, 1998 October 7 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Data Reports - percent of number of DP when jury failed to find mitigation, 1998 October 7 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Data Reports - white victim 2, 1998 October 8 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, notes - Insert 139 materials, 1998 October 8-15 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Data Reports - Race only, 1998 October 9 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Data Reports - Black defendant with non-black, 1998 October 12 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, data reports - Hispanic inserts, 1998 October 12-20 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Data Reports - Main model, 1998 October 13 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - George Woodworth onm ethnicity variables statistical significance, 1998 October 14 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Data Reports - Death J, 1998 October 15 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Data Summeries - Race of Victim, 1998 October 15 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Data Reports -R2 runs, 1998 October 15 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Data Reports - AgNoMit, 1998 October 15-16 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Data Reports - Race of victim, 1998 October 15-16 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence - Neil Weiner, insert on ethnicity variables and statistical significance, 1998 October 19 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Data Reports - Distribution of race and ethnicity, 1998 October 19 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Data Reports - Ptrial runs, 1998 October 19 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Data Reports - Main Effect with black defendant, non black victim, 1998 October 20 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Data Reports - Mitigation finding hypothesis, 1998 October 20 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Data Reports - Reg contracts, PTDTH-JR, 1998 October 20 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Data Reports - Reg contracts, PT Weigh3, 1998 October 20 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, Notes - Interactions Insert A, 1998 October 20-22 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Data Reports - Contracts, Alt with RSK, 1998 October 21 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Data Reports - Ptrial, defendant victim interactions, 1998 October 21 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Data Reports - Regression Contracts, Death J, 1998 October 21 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Data Reports - Defendant victim interaction cross tabs, 1998 October 22 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Data Reports - runs with beach trials, 1998 October 26 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, literature - Aaron Goldstein, the "Hispanic" problem, 1998 October 26 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Data Reports - NoMit D-J, 1998 October 26 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Data Reports - AgNoMit by Broad race, 1998 October 27 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Data Reports - Broad Race/ Def, Death-J, PTDTH-JR, 1998 October 27 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Data Reports - data base corrections, 1998 October 27 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Data Reports - Hispanic/white contcyt, George Woodworth, 1998 October 27 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence - George Woodworth, Cornell Law Review Draft, 1998 October 29 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Data Reports - Ethnicity issues AgNoMit5, Race only, 1998 October 29 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Data Reports - Table G-1, 1998 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Data Reports - Table G-2, 1998 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Data Reports - Table H-1, 1998 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Data Reports - Table H-2, 1998 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Data Reports - Table 7, 1998 November 3; 1998 January 29 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Data Reports - Table 11, 1998 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Data Reports - Table 12, 1998 November 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Data Reports - Table 2, 1998 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Data Reports - Table 3, 1999 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Data Reports - Table 4, 1998 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Data Reports - Table 4, 1998 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Data Reports - Table 4, 1998 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Data Reports - Table 5, 1998 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Data Reports - Table 6, 1998 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Data Reports - Table 9, 1998 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Data Reports - Table 10, 1998 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Data Reports - Table D-1, 1998 November 6 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Data Reports - Table D-1, 1998 November 6 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Data Reports - Table E-1, 1998 November 6 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Data Reports - Table E-2, 1998 November 6 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Data Reports - AGNOMIT5 2RS, 1998 December 4 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Data Reports - Cornell Footnotes, 1998 December 4 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Data Reports - DEATH-J 3RS, 1998 December 4 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Data Reports - PTDTH-JR 2RS, 1998 December 4 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Data Reports - PTWEIGH 3 2RS, 1998 December 4 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Cornell Law Review, drafts of tables, ca. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Data Collection Instrument (DCI), ca. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - David C. Baldus, et. Al, "Racial Discrimination and the Death Penalty in the Post-Formun Era - An Empirical and Legal Overview, with recent findings from Philadelphia,", 1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Defendant Lists - Black Hispanic Defendants, ca. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Defendant Lists - Black non-Hispanic Defendants, ca. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Defandant Lists - Black Non-Hispanics Defandants (Random Sample), ca. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Defandant Lists - white Hispanic Defendants, ca. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Defandant Lists - white Hispanic Defendants, ca. 1998 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Defendant Lists - white Hispanic defendants, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Defandant Lists - white Hispanic Defendants, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Draft Inserts - Barbara Broffitt and David Zuckerman, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Drafts - earlier inserts, 101, 106, 149, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Early plots - Figure 2 AGNOMit3, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Lergh Bienen New Jersey Report excerpt - Individual case adjustments, Niel Alan Weiner, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Master Lists pd Death Penalty cases in Philadelphia Study, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Notes - Data screen method new variables, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Notes - Dingrosites, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Screen variables, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Table draft - race disparities in death sentencing, ca. 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Multiple victim DCI, 1999 February 20 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Report to the Pennsylvania Senate Judiciary Committee - "Recent Evidence of Racial Discrimination in the Administration of Capital Punishment in the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania", 2000 February 22 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Barbara Broffitt's Log of Computing Jobs (January 1997-June 2000), ca. 2000 June (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Sample Sizes Update, 2001 November 7 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Data Reports - DEATH-J 2RS, 2004 December 4 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Barbara Broffitt's Log of Computing Jobs (January 1997-June 2000), Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Barbara Broffitt's Log of Computing Jobs (January 1997-June 2000), Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Blank Philadelphia Charging and Sentencing Study DCI, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Case Lists, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Case Lists, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Earlier Data Collection Instruments (DCIs), Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Mitigating Factors Access Database, Undated (Floppy-disk 10, Item 5-8)
    - Notes - Defending Death Title VI, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Notes - Howard Gittins, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Notes - McArthur Fund, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Notes - Statistical Issues, Lisrel[?] weights, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Notes - variable construction, PT flow variables, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ratio Measures, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Omitted variables Matrix, Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Severity Study, 1996-2001; 11.2; 3
    The Severity Study series contains the experiment and varibles with test data. The data tables and blank surveys are also represented here.
    - Data Reports- Models with hung and No Agg, 1996 December 20-23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Experiment #1, 1997 January 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Experiment #2, 1997 January 17; 1997 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Experiment #3, 1997 January 17; 1997 February 23; 1997 June 04 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Data Reports- Experiment Case lists, 1997 February 16-18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Experiment #1A, 1997 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondance-Instructions for Thumbnail Sketches, 1997 February (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Pre Pre Test Instruction Drafts, 1997 February - March (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Pre Pre Test Masters, 1997 March 17; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondance, Data Summaries- Sampling Plans, 1997 March 24; 1997 March 14 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Notes, Case Lists- Experiment Sampling Issues, 1997 March (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Pre Pre Test Copies and Instructions, 1997 March (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Uncomplete Pre-Test Surveys, ca. 1997 March (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Data Reports- Pre Pre Test, 1997 April 17; 1997 April 22; 1997 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence- David Baldus, George Woodworth memos, 1997 April 18; 1997 May 20; 1997 July 23 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Pre Pre Test Answer Sheet, 1997 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Notes, Appendix A, Answer Sheets, 1997 April (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Notes- PA Planning, 1997 April; 1997 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Pre Pre Test Data, 1997 April (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Card Information, 1997 May 2; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence- David Zuckerman, 1997 May 12; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence- Homicide Severity Study Experiment Research Design, 1997 May 20; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence- Paul McDermott, 1997 May 20; 1997 June 3 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence- Research Design and Rational for the First Homicide Sentencing Severity Experiment, 1997 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Data Summaries, Notes- Sampling, 1997 May 20; 1997 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Instruction/Revised, 1997 May 20; 1997 May 29; 1997 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Nancy Jones, Severity Study Instructions, 1997 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Research Design, Instructions, Answer Sheet, 1997 May (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Notes- Neil Weiner, 1997 May (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Experiment Outcome, May 1997 run, 1997 May (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Pretest Data, 1997 May; 1997 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Thumbnails, 1997 May (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Answer Sheet, 1997 June 5 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Data Reports- Pre-test Results, 1997 June 27 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Instructions, 1997 June 28-30 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Data Reports, notes- Anchor Case Analysis, 1997 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Data Reports- Score/ Severity/ Alternitives, 1997 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Survey Instructions, 1997 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Airlic Masters, 1997 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Airlic House Follow Up, 1997 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Survey Packets, 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Uncompleted Survey Packets, ca. 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Uncompleted Survey Packets, ca. 1997 June (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Data Reports- 5 level Scale, 1997 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence- Letters to Defense Counsel, 1997 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Data Reports- Correlation Analysis, 1997 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Data Summaries- Deck Reliabilities, 1997 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Experiment Expenses, 1997 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Instructions, 1997 July 5 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Data Reports- Pre-test Results, Imputation, 1997 July 8-11 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Background Information, 1997 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Data Reports - Severity Scale, 1997 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Data Reports-Experiment Pre-test, 1997 July 21 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence- George Woodworth, 1997 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Uncompleted Surveys, ca. 1997 July (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Completed Answer Sheets, Data Reports, ca. 1997 July (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Data reports- Severity Scales, 1997 July (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Uncompleted Surveys, ca. 1997 July (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Presentation- Legal Defense Fund Capital Punishment Conference, Handout, 1997 August 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Defenders/ Airlic, 1997 August; 1997 October (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence- Scaling Study, Deck Cases, 1997 September 10; 1997 October 9 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Rating Instructions and Illustrative Survey Packet, 1997 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Invitation Letter, 1997 October 20 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Great Appliction, Proposal, 1997 October 20 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Proposal, IRB, 1997 October (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Joror Instruments, 1997 October; 1998 April (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Experiment Assignement Numbers, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Experiment #2 answer sheet, ca. 1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Hypothetical Case Research, ca.1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Instructions- Table 2, ca.1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Literature- Marvin E. Wolfgang Study, ca. 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Literature- Peter H. Rossi and Andy B. Anderson, ca. 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Notes- Neil Weiner, ca. 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Notes- Pre Pre Test Results, ca.1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Pre Pre Test Answer Sheets, ca.1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Pre Pre Test Sample, ca.1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Rank in Method Pilot, Appendix B, ca.1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Defenders/ Airlic- Mail list, 1998 January 2 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Data Reports- Murder Severity Runs Crosstabs, 1998 March 17 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Data Reports- Add Ag FND 3, 1998 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Data Reports, 1998 April 13 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Data Reports- Correlation on Philadelphia Severity Study, 1998 April 28 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Data Reports- Scores and Lists, 1998 April 28; 1998 September 20; 1998 September 29 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Data Reports- Murder Severity Correlations, 1998 April 30; 1998 May 4 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Data Reports- Table 9 data, Pre test Scales, 1998 April 30 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, Case lists- Inventory of Ag No Mit 5 cases, 1998 July 8; 1998 July 22 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - A Typology of Statutory and Non- Statutory Mitigating Circumstances, 1998 July 15 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Data Reports- Beach Marks, 1998 July24 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Data Reports - Imputation Screens, Race Screens, 1998 September 16 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Data Reports- Imputation Screens, 1998 September 15-16 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Data Reports- Murder Severity Screens, 1998 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 36)